CHRISTIAN RUIZ

DEVELOPER





+57 310-867-2765



christianjavieruizcortes@gmail.com



mugen-portfolio.vercel.app

PROFILE

Front-end web developer with almost 3 years of experience, passionate and dedicated to staying up to date with the latest trends and tools in technology. I am confident in my ability to contribute positively to any development team.

SKILLS

- Html
- Css: Sass, Bem, Itcss, Bootstrap, **Tailwind**
- Javascript
- React js: Hooks, Context, Redux
- Next is
- · Node js: Express
- Nest is
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Scrum
- Tools: VS Code, GIT, Figma

Web Design

EDUCATION

SYSTEM TECHNIQUE

SENA

2019 - 2021

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

Programate

2022 - 2023

SELF-TAUGHT

Internet research

2020 - Present

LANGUAJES

SPANISH: NATIVE

ENGLISH: CERTIFIED C1

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Educamás

2021 - 2022

- Design and development of various web aplications
- web application maintenance
- web application optimization

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance

2020 - Present

· Development of different web applications focused mainly on the frontend

PRODUCT OWNER

Educamás

2022 - 2022

- Make product and roadmap decisions based on business and user needs.
- Work with the development team to ensure delivery of value to the customer.
- interact with the customer and transform their needs into requirements for the product

WEB DEVELOPER

Shark Technology

2023 - 2023

- Web desing
- Development of various web aplications
- · web application optimization